Jack Volontyr

Ruby on Rails Junior Developer

Odesa, Ukraine | 0732090275 | jack.volontyr@gmail.com

github.com/JackVolontyr github.io/guest/index.html

Summary

I'm a Frontend Developer with over 3 years of experience.

I've been working on a Ruby on Rails project as frontend-side software developer over 1.5 years.

I have a year of freelance experience.

Now I want to develop as a Ruby on Rails programmer.

Work experience

Software Developer

1.2017 - 12.2018

DIGIS

Development of fundraise service iamaction.com for Palsio, a Canadian company. Work with professional designers and programmers.

Acquaintance with Ruby on Rails project, component approach, testing and many cool things.

Plus, a lot of projects with React stack, Javascript and many more.

Accomplishments:

- Frontend side for Rails project (¡Query).
- Created components and functionalities with Mountain View and StimulusJs.
- Created light adaptive web pages by mockup.
- Redesigned company portal by re-branding goals.
- Provided work help to all members of company team.

Frontender 2.2016 - 1.2017

Freelance

Worked with a lot of clients from post Soviet Union region.

Accomplishments:

- Self-management.
- Pdf to html/css job, adaptive, mobile first.
- Javascript coding.
- ¡Query plugin integration.
- WordPress content management.

Education

Ruby on Rails 9.2018 - Present

Self-education, online courses.

Course Project - online ticket sales service with chat support functionality: https://tutu-just.herokuapp.com

JavaScript/DOM/Interfaces

6.2016 - 8.2016

Learn Javascript



Skills

- Ruby on Rails
- TDD/BDD with RSpec, acceptance testing
- JavaScript / ECMAscript / CoffeeScript
- HTML5, CSS3, css3 animation, SCSS/LESS, BEM, flexbox/grid, mobile first
- (My)SQL, Posgresql
- Fabric.js (canvas animation/constructor)
- Phaser.js (game engine on canvas and webGL)
- Webpack/Gulp
- Git
- Linux

All from this: https://htmlacademy.ru/courses

Master of technology for primary processing, standardization 2010 - 2015 and certification of raw materials and products of light industry.

Kherson National Technical University Kherson, Ukraine